Come on get it to show how to be the arasuous friend you still don't mean that a girl come to the world that is to old
Where everybody seems to call Come on get it to show how to be the arasuous friend you still don't mean that a girl come to the world that is to old
Where everybody seems to call We're rolling this whole to old we call world for some goal to pose your 50 cents a boom
So come to my home and show some of your love for my own the boys you're on my whole world you're able to hear how cruel this has been about here
Some boys will laugh it's unfair to rather help myself we're still young but the dust isn't close to come along
Come on get it to show how to be the arasuous friend you still don't mean that a girl come to the world that is to old
Where everybody seems to call Come on get it to show how to be the arasuous friend you still don't mean that a girl come to the world that is to old
You're still dumbing at a girl come to the world that is to old
Where everybody seems to call
Come on get in and show how to beat it, I'd rise your spirit
You're still dumbing at a girl come to the world that is to old
Where everybody seems to call